wiknix.com 2012-10-14

# Privacy Policy | Wiknix

We Respect our users’ privacy and we are committed to safeguarding their privacy while online at Wiknix.com. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for Wiknix.com.  

At Wiknix.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by Wiknix.com and how it is used.  
**  
**  
**1\. INFORMATION WE COLLECT**  
****

**A.Log Files**

Like many other Web sites, Wiknix.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**B.Contact Via Email**

If a user wishes to communicate with us they must supply an email address and name in order to use our [contact us](mailto:dbokhiriya\[at\]gmail.com) page.

**  
**  
**2.DATA SECURITY**  
**  
**  
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.  
**  
**  
**3.CHILDREN’S PRIVACY**  
**  
**  
Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 14, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 14.  
**  
**  
**4.COOKIES AND WEB BEACONS**  
**  
**  
Wiknix.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.  

**A.DoubleClick DART Cookie**

\- Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on Wiknix.com.

\- Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to Wiknix.com and other sites on the Internet.   
\- Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL: [http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html ](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)  
**  
**  
Some of our advertising and affiliated partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include :   
**  
**  
**\- Google Adsense**  
**  
**  
From time-to-time, we may embed text or image hyperlinks to these advertisers and affiliated partners, and we may be compensated for views, clicks or purchases made via these hyperlinks.  

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on Wiknix.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.  
**  
**  
Wiknix.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.  

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. Wiknix.com’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.  

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.  

**B.Links**

This website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this website. ****

**C.Contact Information**

If Users Any Question about our privacy policy, Please [Contact Us](mailto:dbokhiriya\[at\]gmail.com).
